Just a bruise on weekends, friends on the beach.
Now frustrated drivers fill every side street.
What once was a shortcut is a nightmare now.
All for a ribbon and a political vow.
Proposition K, got it wrong all along.
We're chokin' on the traffic as the parade rolls on.
Cut off our veins to build their outdoor stage.
Sunset and Richmond are burning with rage.
Too loud, too fast, can't sleep, can't last.
Once we had peace off the Great Highway, now it's gridlock on Tuesday, hawking every day.
Incardio's file called it progress for all, but hundreds of neighbors ignore his recall.
No environmental study to say if we're doomed.
Just spikes and the blocks and another ballot consumed.
Five position cake, got it wrong all along.
We're choking on the traffic as the parade malls are cut off on days to build their outdoor states.
Sunset in Richmond, I'm burning with grace.
Too loud, too fast, if sweet can last.